<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Musea</string>

    <string name="title_home">Main Menu</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Search</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Chats</string>
    <string name="title_user">User</string>
    <string name="title_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="tab_propers">Close to You</string>
    <string name="tab_pais">Country</string>
    <string name="tab_favorits">Favourites</string>
    <string name="titol_exhibitions"><u>Exhibitions</u></string>

    <!-- textos de permisos -->
    <string name="perm_denegado">Permission denied, some functionalities will be limited </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!-- textos para las activities login y signup -->
    <string name="enter_username">Username</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Email</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Password</string>
    <string name="enter_password_twice">Repeat password</string>

    <string name="checkbox_remember_password">Remember me</string>

    <string name="button_login">Login</string>
    <string name="button_signup">Sign up</string>

    <string name="signup_suggestion">Not logged in? Sign up</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">WELCOME TO MUSEA</string>

    <!-- Textos para la vista de busqueda de museos -->
    <string name="recent_text">Recent</string>

    <!-- signup warnings -->
    <string name="warning_used_username">This username is already being used!</string>
    <string name="warning_short_username">The username must have at least 6 characters and a maximum of 22 characters</string>
    <string name="warning_short_username_edit">The username must have at least 6 characters</string>
    <string name="warning_short_bio">The bio must have at least 10 characters </string>
    <string name="warning_used_email">This email is already being used!</string>
    <string name="warning_user_exists">This user already exists!</string>
    <string name="warning_not_email">The email address must be a correct address</string>
    <string name="warning_password">Password must contain minimum 8 characters, at least 1 Upercase, 1 Lowercase and 1 Number</string>
    <string name="warning_not_match_password">Passwords do not match!</string>

    <!-- login warnings -->
    <string name="warning_login">Wrong email or password</string>
    <string name="warning_attempts_exceeded">You have exceeded the number of attempts allowed!</string>
    <string name="remaining_time">seconds left</string>
    <string name="warning_login2">Please enter valid username and password</string>
    <string name="button_eu">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="vis_mus">Visited</string>
    <string name="auto_login_key" />
    <string name="auto_signin_key" />

    <!-- user -->
    <string name="user_pref">Favourites</string>
    <string name="mus_vis">Visited</string>
    <string name="quiz_usu">Quizzes</string>
    <string name="most_visited">Favourite Works</string>
    <string name="change_photo">Change Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="bio">Bio</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="change_val">Save Changes</string>
    <!--Dialog Covid Info-->
    <string name="title_covid">Current Information</string>
    <string name="horari_dialog_covid">Schedule</string>
    <string name="ocupation_text_covid_dialog">Ocupation</string>
    <string name="restriccions_text_dialog_covid">Restrictions</string>
    <string name="points">Points:</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">HOW TO PLAY</string>
    <string name="end_message_gold">¡Master of culture!</string>
    <string name="end_message_silver">Undisputed genius</string>
    <string name="end_message_bronze">First time in culture</string>
    <string name="end_message_garbage">Enough for christmas dinners</string>
    <string name="go_back">go back</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="quizzed_name">Quizzed!</string>


    <!-- Visited -->
    <string name="title_visited">Visited Museums</string>

    <!--Misceláneo-->
    <string name="search_museum">Search museum</string>
    <string name="language_dialog_title">Choose Language</string>
    <string name="your_comment_here">Your comment here…</string>
    <string name="comments_title">Comments</string>

    <!--Delete confirmation dialog-->
    <string name="delete_dialog">Delete</string>
    <string name="delete_confirmation">Are you sure you want to delete?</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="favourites">Favourites</string>

    <string name="search_map">Search...</string>
    <string name="geocode_error">Could not find, try a different spelling or be more specific</string>

    <string name="title_activity_help">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="help_and_privacity">Help and Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="button_premium">Become premium</string>
    <string name="help_general">General</string>
    <string name="help_general_text">Welcome to the help section. Here you will find everything you need to know about Musea. If you think you need more help or want to make a suggestion please send an email to this address (support@musea.com) or by clicking on the button above.\n\nThe Musea application is divided into several sections. First you have the home page. This page will show you the museums near you, those located in the same country you are in and those that you have marked as favorites. You can access the museums by clicking on them.\n\nOnce inside a museum, you can access the different exhibitions available by clicking on them.\n\nYou can also mark it as a favorite by pressing on the heart (♥) that appears at the top of the screen.\n\nIf you want to participate in an exhibition chat, you can join the chat by pressing the speech bubble icon (💬) located at the top right. The chat will appear as available on the chats page. (More information in the chats section)\n\nOnce inside an exhibition you can see the available works by sliding from left to right or vice versa.\n\nYou can bookmark a work by clicking on the heart (♥) that appears at the bottom.\n\nTo access the comments of a work, click on the button in the form of a speech bubble (💬). (More information in the comments section)\n\nTo listen to the audio description of the work (only premium users) press on the button in the shape of a horn (📣).\n\nFrom the main page you can access the quizzes by clicking on the trophy at the top. (More information in the quizzes section).</string>
    <string name="help_usuarios_premium">Premium Users</string>
    <string name="help_usuarios_premium_text">Premium users have certain advantages.\n      - Audio description of all works.\n\nTo be premium you can exchange a number of points (see quizzes) for a certain number of days as a premium user. You can also get a one-year subscription by paying. If you want to subscribe, press ‘Become premium’ on the user page.\n\nIf you think you need more help or want to make a suggestion please send an email to this address (support@musea.com) or by clicking on the button above.</string>
    <string name="help_comentarios">Comments</string>
    <string name="help_comentarios_text">Any type of comment that may be offensive to an individual or group is not allowed. Posting a comment of this nature will be punished with the suspension of the account.\n\nComments can be reported by any user who sees fit, a subsequent review will analyze whether the report has any basis. Reporting without judgment can lead to the suspension of your account.\n\nTo delete a comment, slide from left to right on the comment you want to delete. If it is a comment of yours, you can delete it, otherwise you will be given the option to report the comment.\n\nIf you think you need more help or want to make a suggestion please send an email to this address (support@musea.com) or by clicking on the button above.</string>
    <string name="help_chats">Chats</string>
    <string name="help_chats_text">The same rules apply as in comments.\n\nIf you think you need more help or want to make a suggestion please send an email to this address (support@musea.com) or by clicking on the button above.</string>
    <string name="help_visitar_museos">Visit museums</string>
    <string name="help_visitar_museos_text">If you are in a museum that is registered in our application, you can register your visit from the visited section. Ask an employee where the museum\'s QR is located. Press on the QR scan button to activate the reader. Bring your device close to the QR, once you have read it, the museum will be added to the museums visited.\n\nIf you think you need more help or want to make a suggestion please send an email to this address (support@musea.com) or by clicking on the button above.</string>
    <string name="help_quizzes">Quizzes</string>
    <string name="help_quizzes_text">At the end of a quiz you will get a series of points and a medal depending on the percentage of points you have hit.\n      - 75% → bronze\n      - 85% → silver\n      - 95% → gold\n\nIf you think you need more help or want to make a suggestion please send an email to this address (support@musea.com) or by clicking on the button above.</string>
    <string name="help_mapa">Map</string>
    <string name="help_mapa_text">The Musea application uses the geolocation data of your device to show you the different museums that are located near you. Accept the use of geolocation in order to use this functionality. In no case is this information collected by our team.\n\nOn the map page you can search for museums using the search bar. You can also change your location to be able to consult nearby museums from the main page.\n\nIf you think you need more help or want to make a suggestion please send an email to this address (support@musea.com) or by clicking on the button above.</string>
    <string name="help_pol_tica_de_privacidad">Privacy Policy</string>



</resources>